

KAZAL DATTA

Senior UX | UI & Product Designer **Also Frontend Development**



I'm a UXUI | Product Engineer with more then 11+ years of experience as a in IT agency and strong design educational background. I am a UI/UX designer with a passion for creating beautiful and intuitive experiences for users.

Which are using tools-Adobe illustrator, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe XD, Figma, InVision, UI Design, UIUX Design, Web UI, zeplin, Sketch, Miro, AE, AP, VS Code, MVS, Sublime Text, Notepad++, Atom, Brackets.



CONTACT ME



- +8801715645489
- +8809697390915



Dhaka 1217-Siddheswari, Dhaka



dattakajol1@gmail.com infosetup77@gmail.com



behance.net/dattakajol1



Datta-hub102.github.io/360ZYANSIA1110/



SKILLS

UX | UI | CX | Product | Web | Mobile

Graphic Design | Motion Design

Web Design and Development

Word Press Development (Theme | Plugging)

Flutter | Video Editing

PHP | MySql | Laravel | JavaScript

WORKING EXPERIENCE

1. Senior UXUI & Product Designer also Frontend Developer (12 Month)

(07 Nov, 2022 – 02 Nov, 2023)

Dhaka-BD

I'm Senior UXUI ENGINEER (Web Page / Mobile App / Product Design) (Establish the look and feel for various interfaces, including websites, mobile devices, Product design and mobile apps design.) DESIGNER & ALSO GRAPHIC'S & PROFESSIONAL Expert MINIMALIST LOGO, Digital Banner, Social Media Page, and other DESIGNER SPECIALIST. Highly skilled UXUI designer with 8 years of experience achievement 30% increase in users satisfaction and 45% increase in conventions though the creation in interactive design. Completed jobs 30% before target with 95% client scores in my work previous

2. Senior UXUI Designer (02+ years)

Neoo inc..

Dhaka-BD

(07 Nov, 2020- 31 Oct, 2022)

Highly skilled UXUI designer with 8 years of experience achievement 30% increase in users satisfaction and 45% increase in conventions though the creation in interactive design... Completed jobs 30% before target with 95% client scores in my work previous sector.

3. Senior Graphic & UIUX Designer (04+ years) Wabtec IT Limited

(10 Dec, 2016 - 03 Nov 2020)

Dhaka-BD

AI PS Photo Editing, GRAPHIC'S DESIGN & PROFESSIONAL Expert MINIMALIST LOGO, Digital Banner, Social Media Page, and other DESIGN Sketch SPECIALIST.

4. Senior Graphic Designer (03 years)

Wabtec IT Limited

(03 Jan, 2011 - 01 Dec, 2016)

Dhaka-BD

AI PS Photo Editing, GRAPHIC'S DESIGN & PROFESSIONAL Expert MINIMALIST LOGO, Digital Banner, Social Media Page, and other DESIGN Sketch SPECIALIST.

5. IT & Dishari Manager (03 years)

Nestle Bangladesh Limited

(02 Jan, 2008 - 29 Dec, 2010)

Banking | Vat Exchange | Maintaining | Product Invoice Checking | Dishari Software Order/Unordered Input Output Checking | weekly/Monthly Product Order | Monthly Closing

EDUCATION ATTAINMENT

Masters Administration (MBA) and Business Administration (BBA) National University Of Bangladesh

2014-2016

Subject that we have studied in Masters of Business Administration(MBA) Subject that we have studied in Bachelors of Business Administration(BBA)

Secondary School Certificate(SSC) and Higher Secondary Certificate(HSC) Dhaka Kishoregoni – Board:-Dhaka

2008-2010

Subject that we have studied in Commerce



HONOR AND AWARDS

Coder Trust Bangladesh-Diploma in Full Stack Web Development

2018

CT - INC MERN Stack with TS and Native Android Apps Development

2019/2021

Udemy | Google | Creative IT Institute - User Experience-User Interface 16/17-2020



HOBBIES AND INTEREST













Coding Bike Riding Modeling Playing Guitar Thinking Designing



English



Urdu



Hindi

